hello ladies and gentlemen and welcome
你好，女士们，先生们，欢迎
back I'm your host Walker snipe with
回来我是你的主人沃克狙击与
palo alto education and today we're
帕洛阿尔托教育和今天我们
gonna be talking about video games we
会在谈论我们的视频游戏
might even be playing a little bit of
甚至可能会玩一点点
video games I don't I say might we will
视频游戏我不说我们可以
be the video game we shall be perusing
成为我们将要细读的视频游戏
and using some machine learning
并使用一些机器学习
wonderful stuff on is pac-man pac-man is
奇妙的东西是pac-man pac-man是
a game that looks much like what you see
一个游戏，看起来很像你看到了什么
on your screen but it could easily look
在你的屏幕上，但它可以很容易地看
like this if you had a really intense
像这样， 如果你真的很激烈
graphics card maybe I don't know but
显卡也许我不知道，但
yeah so basically what we're hoping to
耶基本上是我们所希望的
do here is predict tuples that's right
这里做的是预测元组是正确的
ladies and gentlemen tuples tuples is a
女士们，先生们元组元组是一个
fun word is also a mathematical word I'm
有趣的词也是我的数学词
not going to give like the most formal
不会像最正式的那样给予
of definition basically it's like more
的定义基本上就像更多
than one thing right so like you're
一件事情就像你一样
trying to predict one thing that's
试图预测一件事情
called a scalar it's not important
称为标量并不重要
you're trying to predict that one thing
你试图预测那件事
you're trying to predict like two
你试图预测像两个
numbers it's a tuple of numbers or three
数字是一个数字或三个元组
or four or a serious cone you can count
或者你可以计数的四个或一个严重的锥体
so in pac-man it is a two-dimensional
所以在pac-man中它是一个二维的
game we're talking about dimensions
我们正在谈论尺寸的游戏
whereas the stranger things on the
而对陌生人的东西
upside down yeah dimensions are cool you
颠倒是的尺寸很酷你
bet they are so there are two dimensions
打赌他们是这样有两个维度
in pac-man there's up left down and
在pac-man中有剩下的和
right those are the directions those are
对那些就是那些方向
not dimensions the directions are your
不是尺寸的方向是你的
X&Y coordinates so we are trying to
X＆Y坐标，所以我们正在尝试
predict the x and the y value basically
基本预测x和y值
your like like like this way and then
你喜欢这种方式然后
like this way value so what what is
像这样的价值所以是什么
pac-man well it's a game a good start
pac-man， 这是一场比赛，是一个好的开始
and what you're trying to do in this
以及你在这方面想要做什么
game is you're trying to get all the
游戏是你试图让所有的
little blue bits little yellow bits I
小蓝位小黄位I
don't know if the cheese we're gonna
不知道我们要去的奶酪
call them cheese and you want to do this
叫他们奶酪，你想这样做
without doing one very specific thing
没有做一件非常具体的事情
that's common not only in life but also
这不仅在生活中是常见的，而且也是常见的
in other video games this thing that you
在其他电子游戏中这个东西就是你
are trying to not do is die you do not
正试图做不到的事情就是不行
want to die now what could kill you what
现在想死了什么可能会杀了你
you know what are we trying to avoid
你知道我们想要避免什么
that could result in such a terrible
这可能会导致这样一个可怕的
terrible to my as well in this game it
对我来说这很可怕，在这场比赛中呢
is the ghosts not about that paranormal
是幽灵不是关于那超自然的
life in pac-man will have nothing to do
在Pac-Man的生活会无关
with it except occasionally
有时候除外
if these and less superpower up things
如果这些和更少的超级大国起来的东西
and you can eat the ghosts giving you
你可以吃鬼给你
extra bonus points so in that case we
在这种情况下额外的奖励点，我们
are all about those poltergeists but for
都是关于那些poltergeists， 但为了
now we would like to avoid those ghosts
现在我们想避免那些孤魂野鬼
at all cost and this is the problem we
不惜一切代价，这是我们的问题
will be solving today is how to avoid
今天将解决的是如何避免
the ghost we'll be teaching our computer
我们要来教我们的电脑鬼
to avoid the ghosts so let's hop into
避免了鬼让我们跳进
doing that so what we first want to do
这样做是我们第一次想要做的
is want to get to the website get to
是想要到达网站
that website so the website is machine
该网站是这样的网站是机器
learning for kids dot coat UK or just go
为孩子们打点英国外套或者只是去
into your browser of choice and type in
放入您选择的浏览器并输入
machine learning for kids any search
机器学习任何搜索的孩子
engine will do that sir cheese stuff and
发动机会做那个先生奶酪的东西和
it will likely be the first choice so
它可能会是第一选择
once we are here I want to make sure you
一旦我们在这里，我想确保你
login I might mention that later but
登录我可能会在稍后提到，但是
it's just don't forget it because
它只是不要忘记它，因为
otherwise your project won't be saved so
否则你的项目将不会被保存
we want to go to worksheets and that
我们想要去工作表和那个
this is where we will find our fancy
这是我们会发现我们的幻想的地方
pantsy little guide for this product
这款产品的裤子很少
creation we're making here so we are
我们在这里创作的创作就是这样
students today click on that and look at
今天的学生点击并看看
this here we are so this is our sort
这里我们是这样，这是我们的排序
bread and butter swear we already follow
面包和黄油发誓我们已经遵循
along and see what we got
一起看看我们得到了什么
so the first thing we're gonna do you
所以我们要做的第一件事就是你
bet you it we're just we're gonna mess
打赌你，我们只是我们会混乱
around with it we're gonna play with it
与它在一起，我们会玩它
alright so what we want to do to get to
好吧，那么我们想要做什么去
scratch is either type it into your
从头开始是将它输入到你的
browser this this guy right here or you
浏览器这个人在这里或你
can even just click it if you do you
如果你愿意， 甚至可以点击它
should arrive at this website you want
应该到达 你想要的这个网站
to open the project template of pac-man
打开pac-man的项目模板
once you do then we have to mess around
一旦你这样做，我们就得乱七八糟
a little bit with the game itself - some
一点点与游戏本身- 一些
other parts of the game but with the
游戏的其他部分，但与
arrow keys you can maneuver your pac-man
方向键你可以操纵你的太空人
around the board experimenting with what
围绕董事会进行实验
does and does not work as strategies to
做和不做作为策略
avoid the ghost I find the circular
避免我找到圆形的鬼魂
pattern of just going around the map
刚刚绕过地图的模式
works pretty good most of the time but
大部分时间都工作得很好，但是
yeah so this is basically just the game
是的，所以这基本上只是游戏
engine you could say and we survived for
你可以说引擎，我们活了下来
22 removes alrighty so now we have a
22删除好了，所以现在我们有一个
little bit of experience with the actual
一点实际的经验
game playing and kind of just getting a
玩游戏和种类只是得到一个
feel for
同情
but how do we actually represent these
但我们如何真正代表这些
number things going on in our code and
在我们的代码和数据中发生的事情
you know what is the machine learning
你知道什么是机器学习
model that we're creating what exactly
模型，我们正在创造什么
is it gonna be seen what is it look at
它会被看到它在看什么
well what's going to be looking at is
以及将要看到的是
our x and y values for mr pac-man and
我们 的男性和女性的 x和y值
mr. ghost each of these characters in
先生。 幽灵每个这些人物中
our world has an x and y value because
我们的世界有一个x和y值，因为
that determines where they are it's a
决定他们在哪里这是一个
two dimensional world your X and your Y
二维世界你的X和你的Y.
dimension which means that to describe
这意味着要描述的维度
some body or some place there you need
有些身体或某处你需要的地方
two values if you were in three
如果你有三个，那么就有两个值
dimensions you would need three values
尺寸你需要三个值
whoa crazy and this brings us back to
疯狂的，这让我们回到了
that tuple thing we were talking about
那个我们正在谈论的元组事物
to describe the ghost
来形容鬼魂
we need a tuple of two and same for mr
我们需要的两个元组和同为先生
pac-man so pac-man is trying to decide
pac-man等pac-man正在尝试做出决定
this but the machine learning is trying
这但机器学习正在尝试
to figure out is where do I go where do
搞清楚的是我在哪里 哪里
I go I got four options like an up depth
我去了我有四个选项，像一个深度
down left and right and trying to make
左右倾斜并试图制造
the best choice given the state of the
最好的选择给定的状态
coast where's the ghost shouldn't go
海岸鬼在哪里不应该去
there kind of the basic gist of that all
这一切的基本要点都有
right so for this next bit we want to
对于我们想要的下一个比特就是这样
hop into creating our project that's
跳入创建我们的项目
what we're gonna do so we want to leave
我们会怎么做， 所以我们想离开
mr. scratch we want to go over to
先生。 我们想要去划伤
machine learning for kids the normal
机器学习为孩子们正常
websites I guess you could say and we
我想你可以说我们的网站
want to add a new project at your first
想在你的第一个项目中添加一个新项目
make sure that you were logged in is
请确保你在是记录
this important otherwise all your work
这个重要的，否则所有的工作
will not be saved and will be sad and
将不会被拯救，并会伤心和
let's just not do that so login then add
让我们不这样做，登录然后添加
a new project names mine pac-man you may
一个新的项目命名我的pac-man你可能
name yours whatever you prefer we're
无论你喜欢什么，我们都会为你命名
recognizing numbers and we're going to
识别号码，我们将会
create four classes in each of these we
在每个这些我们创建四个类
will name them up town left and right I
将他们命名为城镇左右我
hope that you were familiar with these
希望你熟悉这些
directions they're pretty important now
方向他们现在是非常重要的
we are going to create some of the code
我们要创造一些 代码
for this thing so we want to go back to
对于这件事情，所以我们想回去
scratch and we have our fancy pantsy a
从头开始，我们有我们的花式裤子a
little worksheet guide right here and
小工作表指南就在这里和
what we want to do
我们想要做什么
as we have our pac-man template open
因为我们打开了我们的pac-man模板
this is big time-saver here I'll tell
这是我要说的很大的节省时间
you what and with our more blog section
你什么和我们更多的博客部分
we want to change some things around
我们想改变一些东西
right so we have this code actually okay
对，所以我们有这个代码实际上没问题
here eat some housekeeping that I didn't
这里吃了一些家务，我没有
realize that I should have realized and
意识到我应该已经意识到
I didn't and I would like to share with
我没有，我想分享一下
you so you might be looking at this and
你所以你可能会看这个和
like all right it's it's telling me to
就像它告诉我的那样
look for this thing and it's not here
寻找这个东西，它不在这里
what's wrong I will see it well there
怎么了， 我会在那里看到它
are different little areas so you can
是不同的小区域，所以你可以
click here and see it it's right here if
点击这里，看看它在这里如果
you're looking for this thing or
你正在寻找这个东西或
whatever so rows portion we want to be
无论我们想要成为什么样的行
in this stage jokes cuz it's called the
在这个阶段开玩笑， 因为它被称为
stage thank great jokes so good yes we
感谢伟大的笑话这么好，我们
do that and we want to alter our win up
那样做， 我们想改变我们的胜利
arrow key pressed script to go the up
箭头键按下的脚本走上去
that we have defined what we're doing
我们已经定义了我们正在做的事情
here is we're collecting data right so
这里是我们正在收集数据的权利
we're learning from our own play pac-man
我们从我们自己的玩家pac-man中学习
will learn after you and the way we do
将在你和我们的方式之后学习
that is when the up arrow key is pressed
即按下向上箭头键时
set the next pac-man move to up but this
设置下一个pac-man的动作，但这个
is the up remember that little those
是记得那些小的那些
like buckets that you made a little bit
像你做了一点点的桶
ago yeah and like your your training and
以前是啊，喜欢你的训练和
the project and all that this is where
该项目和所有这一切都在哪里
we are storing those things so once we
我们一旦存储了这些东西
play the game a little bit the script
玩一点点剧本 的游戏
that we're modifying now will actually
我们现在要修改的是实际的
store the games that we played and then
存储我们玩过的游戏然后
later we will train the machine learning
稍后我们将培训机器学习
on these games so people learn to play
在这些游戏中让人们学习玩
just like you it's kind of cool
就像你一样，它很酷
so to actually get into the the code
所以要真正进入代码
this is what you want to change here we
这是你想在这里改变我们
have this guy I want to drag these guys
有这个人我想拖这些人
over here I'm not going to go to the
在这里我不打算去
full extent of that right now because
现在的全部范围， 因为
we're gonna move quick nothing you want
我们会快速移动任何你想要的
to do is adjust this dude right here
要做的就是在这里调整这个家伙
which is one of these I believe the
这是其中之一 ，我相信了
pac-man move yes the control the pac-man
pac-man移动是控制pac-man
move pac-man move is right here
移动pac-man移动就在这里
we won't alter yes yes yes again you're
我们不会改变是的是的是再次你是
just dragging are you dropping
只是拖着你在滴
boom so once we've done all this then
繁荣，所以一旦我们完成了所有这一切
change your pac-man decision this is
改变你的Pac-Man的决定，这是
super important
超级重要
pac-man decision where do you get the
pac-man决定你从哪里得到的
side stuff here he is so what are you
这里边的东西，他是如此的你是什么人
deciding well this big old dude right
很好地决定 这个大老头子的权利
here is the guy and then guess what
这里是这个人，然后猜猜看是什么
guess what guess what these guys are
猜猜这些人是什么猜测
here yes they are you just drag these
这里是的，他们是你只是拖动这些
guys over here like so that is what
你们在这里等，从而 是什么
we're doing all right we have done this
我们做得很好，我们已经做到了
awesome awesome awesome awesome so we
真棒真棒真棒所以我们
got we got all made now what is left is
得到了我们所有的东西，现在剩下的是
to play the game and collect some data
玩游戏并收集一些数据
so now what you're gonna do is you to
所以现在你要做的是你
play the game now play well do not take
现在玩游戏玩得不好
this lightly this is very serious
这轻微这是非常严重的
business here and take our game playing
这里的业务和我们的游戏玩
very seriously play it play the game and
非常认真地玩它玩游戏和
avoid the ghosts as best as you can try
尽量避免鬼魂，尽可能地尝试
and mix in a good mixture of up down
并混合上下混合
left sand rights because you won't have
因为你不会有 左沙权
at least 10 of each Walker how do you
每个沃克至少有10个，你怎么样
know I found out the hard way yes it did
知道我发现了艰辛的道路是它做
you can play this game without like ever
你可以玩这个游戏，而不会像以前一样
going down apparently and it works
显然会下降，它的工作
pretty well
很不错
who knew yes do that and then once you
谁知道是的，然后一旦你
do so stop the game save the project and
这样做就停止游戏保存项目和
we're moving on alright now we're going
我们正常的移动上，现在我们要去
to the fun part you betcha ladies and
到好玩的部分你betcha女士们
gentlemen we're about to experience the
我们即将要体验的绅士们
magic of machine learning so what we
机器学习的神奇，所以我们
want to do is leave scratch go back to
想要做的就是留下划痕回去
our projects which we see here we're
我们的项目，我们在这里看到我们
gonna click on our good friend pac-man
要点击我们的好朋友pac-man
we're gonna go to train and we're gonna
我们要去训练，我们会去的
see that hopefully this is what we see
希望这是我们所看到的
that we have collected data look at this
我们收集的数据看这个
we have our tuples
我们有我们的元组
liang'er tuples to describe the state of
两个元组描述的状态
the game we need four values because we
游戏中我们需要四个值，因为我们
have pac-man and our ghost the both
有pac-man和我们的幽灵两者
two-dimensional 2+2 is or yay
二维2 + 2是或者是耶
so fever back an x value pac-man Y goes
所以退烧一个x值pac-man Y会去
to X goes to Y and we have a bunch of
到X去Y，我们有一堆
these data points as each these are only
这些数据点仅作为每一个
one data point as far as the machine
一个数据点直到机器
learning goes and we have them for the
学习去，我们有他们的
game so we like have
游戏，所以我们喜欢有
a series of gameplays that if you played
如果你玩过一系列的游戏
well are a pretty good way to avoid the
以及避免这种情况是一个很好的方法
ghosts now what does this mean it means
鬼现在这意味着什么
we can go and train our model I want to
我们可以去训练我们的模型，我想
go over to learn and test and this is
去学习和测试，这是
where the magic of machine learning
机器学习的魔力在哪里
happens now this looks a little
现在发生这看起来有点
different because I've already done the
不同，因为我已经完成了
training but you're gonna do it so it'll
训练， 但你会做到这一点，所以它会
take a little while but once it is done
花一点时间，但一旦完成
well then we get to test it out don't we
那么我们就来测试一下吧
alright we are almost there almost of
好吧，我们几乎在那里
the precipice of a success so what we're
成功的绝境，所以我们是
going to do let's go back to scratch we
要做我们回去抓我们
have our machine learning model it's
有我们的机器学习模式
super smart it's super awesome
超级聪明， 它超级棒
so we're gonna go back to scratch and
所以我们要回去抓
we're gonna open up that project we made
我们会打开 我们制作的项目
earlier Pac Man guy just don't here so
早些时候吃豆人的家伙就不在这里
you know once we do this you want to
你知道，一旦我们这样做， 你想
change some things around okay because
改变周围的没关系，因为一些事情
it's no longer us who are playing the
我们不再是谁玩了
game so when we press a little arrow
游戏，所以当我们按下一个小箭头
keys we don't want nothing to happen we
键，我们别无所求发生我们
want it to make decisions so that's what
希望它做出决定，所以这就是事实
we're gonna change you so the first
我们会改变你的第一个
thing we want to do is take out any
我们想要做的是拿出任何东西
interaction we have which I've already
我们已经有了相互作用
done actually so I will show you here
所以我会在这里给你看
these guys these gentlemen right here
这些男士们就在这里
what you want to get rid of because
你想摆脱的是因为
you're no longer pressing the keys it's
你不再按它的键
going to be pressing the keys itself
将自己按下按键
basically to get rid of those and you
基本上是为了摆脱那些和你
want to modify your pac-man decision to
想要修改你的pac-man决定
use the block never too much completely
使用块永远不嫌多完全
nothing you want to use the model we
没有什么你想用我们的模型
just made you want it to use the smart
只是让你想要它使用智能
machine learning stuff that we just
机器学习的东西，我们只是
created so we do that fill it out just
创建， 所以我们做，只是填写它
like this make sure everything is
像这样确保一切
correct small differences can't make a
正确的小差异不能使一个
big difference
差别很大
then what want to do is this is
那么什么想做的是，这是
literally just for time saving this
从字面上来说只是为了节省时间
little wait a second there's no reason
等一下， 没有理由
to wait a second you just want it to go
等待一秒钟， 你只是想让它走
we want a seat in action so get rid of
我们要在行动座位所以摆脱
that gun and then I believe we're ready
那枪，然后我相信我们已经准备好了
alright so saver project is gonna save
好的，这样保存项目就可以保存
your work and then this should work it
你的工作， 然后这应该工作
does work look at this look at this
看看这个看起来有用吗？
we'll get a full screen we'll get a full
我们将获得一个全屏，我们会得到一个完整的
screen check this out I'm not doing
屏幕检查了这一点，我没有做
nothing I'm not doing nothing nobody
没有我没有做任何事
this is pretty cool right it's learned
这是非常酷的权利，这是学习
fairly well apparently it thinks it's
显然它认为它是
trying to get to the top corner I don't
试图到达角落我不知道
know if that's like a sub-goal but 421
知道这就像一个分目标，但421
moves it avoids the ghost I don't know
移动它避免了 我不知道 的幽灵
if I tested this did we test this so we
如果我测试了这个，我们测试这个，所以我们
can show here this is pretty cool as
可以在这里展示这是非常酷的
well that it will take 11 slow moves
以及它将需要11个缓慢的举动
this is a little weight thing happens
这是有点重量的事情发生
thinks 11 moves yes for the ghost to get
认为11招是让鬼魂得到的
to pac-man with our machine learning it
与我们的机器学习它的 pac-man
now takes 21 that's fierce makes no
现在需要21，这是激烈的使不
difference double so with the amazing
差异是惊人的一倍
machine learned we've done we have
我们已经完成了机器学习
doubled the time it takes that's so cool
把时间缩短了一倍，非常酷
all right so what what have we done here
好，那么我们在这里做了什么
with this project we have played pac-man
在这个项目中，我们玩过pac-man
a good start to all to all machine
所有机器都是一个良好的开端
learning projects place and video games
学习项目地点和视频游戏
in all seriousness though a ton of
尽管一切都很严肃
machine learning research is in the
机器学习研究在
video game world which is kind of cool I
电子游戏世界这是一种很酷的我
enjoy that but we've trained Packman to
尽情享受，但我们已经培训了Packman
recognize the state of the world and to
认识世界和状态
make a decent decision of how to get
做一个体面的决定如何得到
away from the ghosts pretty cool this is
远离鬼魂，这很酷
actually a super useful thing for so
其实这是一个超级有用的东西
many things whether you're trying to
很多事情， 无论你想要
figure out mapping data or literally
找出映射数据或从字面上
anything in whatever dimensions and
任何尺寸和尺寸的东西
you're trying to get around and make a
你试图绕过去做一个
decision I know that sounded like really
我知道这个决定听起来像是真的
general and kind of useless but that's
一般和有用的， 但那是
if something sounds really general
如果听起来真的很普遍
account of useless it's probably really
无用的帐户可能是真的
important and gonna help the world out a
重要的，并会帮助世界
whole lot besides that let's let's take
除此之外，我们再来看看
a note of what our machine learning did
记下我们的机器学习做了什么
here if we if we watch it it seems to
在这里，如果我们看到它似乎
make the same moves over and over
一遍又一遍地做同样的动作
doesn't it it always takes 21 moves and
难道它总是需要21次移动和
it always takes the same pattern there's
它始终以相同的模式有
a word for this in machine learning it's
在机这个词学习它的
called overfitting and it's a bad thing
所谓的过学习，这是一个坏事
okay it's a bad thing what it means is
好吧，这意味着什么是一件坏事
that on the data you've collected so in
这对数据你收集所以在
this instance it's the video games that
这个例子就是视频游戏
we played the times we played is looked
我们玩了我们玩的时间看起来
at that and it's basically
在那个基本上
memorized right the teacher the teacher
背对老师的老师
the teacher gave you the sheets what she
老师把你的单子给了你
needed to know and you memorized what
需要知道和你记住了什么
was on that sheet and immediately after
在那张纸上，之后
the test you forgot everything and this
测试你忘了一切和这个
is a shame it's sad because we're not
是一种耻辱这是可悲的，因为我们不是
trying to memorize the information we're
试图记住我们的信息
trying to learn we're trying to get a
试图学习我们试图得到一个
machine learning model that generalizes
一般化 的机器学习模型
that's good at pac-man you know pac-man
这对你说pac-man的 pac-man很有用
has many levels look we got this one and
有很多层面看我们得到这个和
there are so many other ones and you
有很多其他人和你
don't want it to be just good at just
不希望它只是在善于处理
one pac-man level you want to be good at
一个Pac-Man的水平，你要善于
pac-man right so what this probably
pac-man权利所以这可能是什么
means is that if nothing else we want to
意思是说，如果没有其他我们想要的
collect more data again I said we're
再次收集更多数据我说我们是
gonna be saying that a lot but there are
会说很多，但有
likely other things we want to do this
很可能我们想要做的其他事情
is not an easy problem even though maybe
即使可能，也不是一个容易的问题
it felt easy but it's actually really
它感觉很简单，但它确实是真的
complicated so this is um have an open
复杂所以这是UM有一个开放
research area in a sense but here we see
研究领域在某种意义上， 但在这里我们看到
a perfect example of overfitting and at
一个完美的例子，过度适应和
least one solution to this is grabbing
至少有一个解决方案是抓住
some more data but there are others many
一些更多的数据， 但也有很多
many many others so once again thank you
许多其他人再次感谢你
very much for joining us I am Walker
非常适合加入我们，我是沃克
Skype with Palo Alto education and I
Skype与帕洛阿尔托教育和我
hope that you have a stupendous day
希望你有一个惊人的一天
thank you and goodbye
谢谢你， 再见